<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My blogs on Personal website of Akil Elkamel</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My blogs on Personal website of Akil Elkamel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 06:09:13 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data manipulation with dplyr</title>
      <link>/blog/dplyr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 06:09:13 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/dplyr/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science</title>
      <link>/blog/data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 06:09:13 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/data-science/</guid>
      <description>This is a post written in plain Markdown (*.md) instead of R Markdown (*.Rmd). The major differences are:
 You cannot run any R code in a plain Markdown document, whereas in an R Markdown document, you can embed R code chunks (```{r}); A plain Markdown post is rendered through Blackfriday, and an R Markdown document is compiled by rmarkdown and Pandoc.  There are many differences in syntax between Blackfriday&amp;rsquo;s Markdown and Pandoc&amp;rsquo;s Markdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Story with R</title>
      <link>/blog/my-story-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 05:09:13 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/my-story-with-r/</guid>
      <description>I will start by speeking how did i know R for the first time. I remember it was in the second year of my engineering degree in computer science. Me and my classmates knew R in the course of knowledge engineering. In 2007/2008, i was in my second year in my M.Sc. degree, and my supervisor was our instructor of the knowledge engineering course who was a very competent teacher and supervisor and who loves her job.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>